

(naukri com





PMP Certified Project Manager, Certified Scrum Master with 16 Years in IT Industry out of which 11 Years in managing end to end delivery of projects within allocated schedule & budget.



Total Experience: 16 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Trivandrum, Kochi

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Project Mgr-IT/Software

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: IT Project Management, Delivery Management, PMP, Scrum Master, AWS, CSM, ERP, PMO, Project Management, Business Analysis, SDLC, Cloud, Risk Management, Agile, Conflict Management, MS Office, SAAS, Project Planning, E-commerce, Python, Program Management

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21

Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Work Authorization

Summary

PMP Certified Project Manager with overall 16 Years of experience in IT industry out of which 11 Years in Project Management role. I did my B. Tech in Computer Science and Engineering from University of Calicut, Kerala. Certified Scrum Master (CSM) from Scrum Alliance.

Work Experience

- Edkal Technologies Pvt Limited (www.edkal.com) as Technical Lead Dec 2018 to Jul 2020
- o Responsible for end-to-end Project Management , Create Project Plan, Setup and Manage a team of 14 UI developers, Project Governance.
- o Responsible for Delivery of Angular material design & API integration with Mcro Services and callout the dependencies
- o Conduct daily stand-ups, Sprint reviews & Sprint retrospectives.
- o Monitor Risks, Issues, Changes, Timelines, Quality Management, VAPT fixes.
- $o\ Prepared\ Operational\ Process\ Tracker,\ Operation\ Process\ Metrics,\ Daily/\ Weekly\ Status\ report\ and\ shared\ with\ senior\ managers.$
- Idea Bean Software Pvt Limited as Project Manager Jul 2016 to Nov 2018
- Edkal Technologies Pvt Limited as Project Manager Nov 2005 to Jun 2015
- Sami Labs as Senior Software Engineer Apr 2005 to Oct 2005
- Software Fusions Limited as Programmer May 2001 to Apr 2003

Responsible for programming the business requirement tasks given by the team lead, custom ERP development projects

^ Back to Top

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

UG: B. I ecnyB.E. (Computers) from University of Calicut, Roznikoge in 2000

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Project Management Professional Certified Scrum Master AWS Certified Solution Architect Associate

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
AWS		2020	3 Year(s)
Office 365		2021	10 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
MS Project		2019	5 Year(s)
JIRA		2021	4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Click up		2021	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Bitbucket		2021	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
MAGENTO	1.9.1.1	2018	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Delivery Management		2020	8 Year(s)
PROJECT MANAGEMENT		2021	11 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Agile Project Management		2020	6 Year(s)
WATERFALL		2017	12 Year(s)
Develop and Track Budget		2020	9 Year(s)
PROCESS IMPROVEMENT		2020	11 Year(s)
SLACK		2021	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
MS Teams		2021	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Cisco webex		2021	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Cross Functional Collaboration		2020	11 Year(s)
RISK MANAGEMENT		2020	11 Year(s)
Stakeholder Management		2020	11 Year(s)
BUSINESS ANALYSIS		2020	16 Year(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓	
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓	

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Category: General US Work Status: Need H1 Visa

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.